raids.com 2014-08-21

# Raids - Entertainment

## **Last Updated: August 5th, 2013**

RAIDS.COM knows your privacy is very important. From time to time, we may change our privacy policy and thus we urge you to re-check this page on a constant basis to ensure that you know if and what these changes are. By continuing to use any part of the RAIDS.COM website after any changes to this policy have been made, you are agreeing to any and all changes made.

## Introduction

RAIDS.COM ("RAIDS.COM") considers your privacy to be of utmost importance.This privacy policy has been adapted from two policies: Google Adsense (Google Inc.) and Automattic (WordPress.com).This privacy policy is under the creative commons sharealike license. Please read and consider this notice very closely.

Website Users

RAIDS.COM, as most website operators do, collects non-personally-identifying information in a manner that web browsers and servers generally make available. This non-personally-identifying information pertains to, but is not limited to: what kind of browser, language preference, referring site, date and time of each visit (and visitor), demographics of every visitor, whether a visitor is new to the site or not, and operating system. We, RAIDS.COM, use this information we gather to better understand our audience, and thus improve the website through new and desired updates and changes. RAIDS.COM may publish information to the public regarding the usage of its website, such as in the form of reported trends of statistics of the website. However, RAIDS.COM will never release personally-identifying information such as your Internet Protocol address (IP Address). 

Again, RAIDS.COM does not use personally-identifying information of its visitors as described above, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

## Collection of Personally-Identifying Information

Many users of RAIDS.COM’ websites make the choice to interact with RAIDS.COM in ways that require RAIDS.COM to aggregate personally-identifying information. The amount or type of information that is necessary depends on the kind of interaction. One example is that we ask visitors who create an account with RAIDS.COM to provide an email address and unique username. In each and every situation, RAIDS.COM collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with RAIDS.COM. RAIDS.COM does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. Visitors are free to deny RAIDS.COM’ access to any personally-identifying information but must understand that it may hinder them from participating in specific website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

RAIDS.COM may gather and examine statistics pertaining to the actions of visitors to its websites. As a couple examples, RAIDS.COM may monitor the most visited posts or the most commented on images. RAIDS.COM may publicly display this information on its websites or share it with others in various forms. RAIDS.COM does not disclose personally-identifying information other than described below.

## Protection of Specific Personally-Identifying Information

9GAG discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on RAIDS.COM’ behalf or to provide services available at RAIDS.COM’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. 

Some of the employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using RAIDS.COM’ websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.   
In some cases we may choose to buy or sell assets. In this type of transaction, user information is typically one of the business assets transferred. If RAIDS.COM, or all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that RAIDS.COM goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any new owner of RAIDS.COM may continue to use your personal and non-personal information only as set forth in this policy. Otherwise, RAIDS.COM will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, RAIDS.COM discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when RAIDS.COM believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of RAIDS.COM, third parties or the public at large. 

If you are a registered user of a RAIDS.COM website and have supplied your email address, RAIDS.COM may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or to simply keep you updated with company and/or website changes. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. RAIDS.COM takes all measures required to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

It is important to be aware that if you submit information to “message boards,” “forums,” or “chat rooms,” such information becomes public information, meaning that you lose any privacy rights you might have with regards to that information. Such disclosures may also increase your chances of receiving unwanted communications (also known as SPAM).

## Cookies and Web Beacons

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. RAIDS.COM uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of RAIDS.COM websites, and their website access preferences. RAIDS.COM visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using RAIDS.COM’ websites, with the understanding that specific features of RAIDS.COM’ websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on RAIDS.COM. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to RAIDS.COM and other sites on the Internet.Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on RAIDS.COM send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. RAIDS.COM has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. RAIDS.COM’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  
Again, if you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options, understanding that specific features of RAIDS.COM’ websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

## Links to Third Parties

This privacy policy is only applicable to information gathered by RAIDS.COM. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that RAIDS.COM does not own or control, or employees that RAIDS.COM does not manage. A RAIDS.COM website may contain links to third party websites. Any information you provide to, or that is collected by, third-party sites may be subject to the privacy policies of those sites, if they have any. You should read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally-identifying information, and RAIDS.COM and its affiliates will not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party.

## Security

All non-personally-identifying information, potentially personally-identifying and personally identifying-information described above is stored on restricted database servers. RAIDS.COM does everything in its power to ensure the safety of such information.

## Opt-Out/Choice

If you would like to enquire about this privacy policy or RAIDS.COM in general, please contact us.

If RAIDS.COM ever sends you information via email about new products, services, or information that you did not request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request no further notifications.

## Contact

If you would like to enquire about this privacy policy or RAIDS.COM in general, please [contact us](http://raids.com/contact.php).

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on RAIDS.COM. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to RAIDS.COM.
